Guide to the University of Pittsburgh Archives Moving Images Collection, ca. 1928-2001 UA.Film.Video
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Sports, I.
  - Football, 3.
    - Video, 648 items
      - "Panther Pride 1990", unknown; Betacam SP 60 Minute (Box 26, Video 519)
      - Panther Pride 1990, VHS T-120 (Box 30, Video 586)
      - Panther Pride 1992 Shows, September 9, 1992 AND October 23, 1992; Betacam SP 60 Minute (Box 22, Video 436)
      - Panther Pride Preseason, unknown; VHS T-120 Needs Case (Box 30, Video 589)
      - Panther Pride - #3 Pitt vs. Illinois, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 (Box 36, Video 729)
      - Pitt - Oklahoma 3rd Quarter/Plus Half of 4th Qt., September 15, 1984; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 (Box 5, Video 1440)
      - "You're In For a Game", unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 30 (Box 5, Video 495)
      - Pitt Football Pitt - WVU 4, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic MBR 20 (Box 5, Video 83)
      - Pitt Football '79 Pitt/Kansas, September 16, 1979; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 30 (Box 5, Video 84)
      - Pitt vs. notre Dame #1 - 1978, 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 (Box 5, Video 82)
      - Pitt/Penn State Football Game Part #3, November 24, 1978; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 (Box 5, Video 1450)
      - Pitt Football - '78 Boston College vs Pitt, 1978; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Kerry Richards (Box 5, Video 1652)
      - Pitt - WVU September 29 3th Qtr, 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Tape 3 of 4? (Box 5, Video 81)
      - Pitt - WVU September 29 4th Qtr, 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Tape 4 of 4? (Box 5, Video 79)
      - Pitt vs. Miami 1961, Betacam SP 30 Minute (Box 5, Video 77)
      - Pitt Athletics - Historical Footage - Football - 1930's, Arnie Sowell, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCA-30BRS Arnie Sowell Don Hennon (Box 7, Video 126)
      - Pitt Pre-Season Show, August 29, 1987; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 7:00-8:00 PM (Box 7, Video 770)
      - 1992 NFL Draft #1, April 26, 1992; Betacam SP 90 Minute Tape 1 of ? (Box 26, Video 512)
      - NFL Draft (1992) #2, April 26, 1992; Betacam SP Big Beta Tape (length unknown) Tape 2 of ? (Box 46, Video 1057)
      - 1992 NFL Draft #3, April 26, 1992; Betacam SP 90 Minute Tape 3 of ? (Box 22, Video 438)
      - 1992 NFL Draft #4, April 26, 1992; Betacam SP 90 Minute Tape 4 of ? (Box 7, Video 437)
      - Steve Apke Profile, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic Needs Case (Box 8, Video 129)
      - Steve Apke Profile, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic Needs Case (Box 9, Video 138)
      - "Paul Hackett Interview for 1992 Highlight Video", unknown; VHS T-120 (Box 43, Video 953)
      - Dorsett on Hackett / Mel Blount Youth Home Wash Co., March 6, 1989; 3/4 Inch U-matic MBR 20 (Box 8, Video 223)
      - Tony Dorsett on Paul Hackett, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCS-20BRS (Box 43, Video 946)
      - Tony Dorsett - ESPN II, October 16, 1995; VHS T-120 (Box 43, Video 965)
      - All That Jazz 1977 (Sugar Bowl), unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 30 P26 (Box 8, Video 335)
      - Great American Champions Feature ( Mike Ditka Univ. of Pittsburgh), December 8, 1987; 3/4 Inch U-matic BCS-10 (Box 8, Video 222)
      - Great American Champions Feature - Mike Ditka Univ. of Pittsburgh, December 8, 1987; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA-10s Needs Case (Box 25, Video 486)
      - "100 Year Interviews W/Matt Cavanaugh 2, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCS-20BRS (Box 8, Video 133)
      - "100 Year Interviews W/ Ave Daniel" 1, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCS-20BRS (Box 8, Video 135)
      - "100 Year Interviews W/Ave Daniel" 2, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCR-20BRS (Box 8, Video 132)
      - 100 Years Pitt Schmidt 2 / Ditka 1, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCS-20BRS (Box 8, Video 134)
      - "100 Year Interviews With Steve Petro", unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCS-20BRS Tape 2 of ? (Box 46, Video 1064)
      - "100 Year Interviews with Steve Petro", unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCS-20BRS Tape 3 of ? (Box 46, Video 1053)
      - "100 Years of Pitt Football" - John Majors Interview Tape 1, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCS-20BRS Tape 1 of ? (Box 46, Video 1060)
      - "100 Years of Pitt Football" - John Majors Interview Tape 2, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCS-20BRS Tape 2 of ? (Box 46, Video 1069)
      - "100 Years of Pitt Football" - John Majors Interview Tape 3, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCS-20BRS Tape 3 of ? (Box 46, Video 1072)
      - "100 Years Pitt" Fazio(1), unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCS-20BRS Tape 1 of ? (Box 46, Video 1061)
      - "100 Years Pitt" Fazio(2), unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCS-20BRS Tape 2 of ? (Box 46, Video 1066)
      - "100 Year Interviews with Joe Walton", unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCS-20BRS Tape 1 of ? (Box 46, Video 1071)
      - "100 Year Interviews with Joe Walters & Wes Posvar"), unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCS-20BRS (Box 46, Video 1062)
      - "100 Years Pitt" Dorsett 1, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCS-20BRS Tape 1 of ? (Box 46, Video 1067)
      - 100 Years Pitt - Dorsett 2, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCS-20BRS Tape 2 of ? (Box 46, Video 1070)
      - "100 Years Pitt" Dorsett 3, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCS-20BRS Tape 3 of ? (Box 46, Video 1068)
      - 100 Years Pitt Dorsett 4, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCS-20BRS Tape 4 of ? Needs Case (Box 8, Video 136)
      - "100 Years Pitt" Dorsett 4 (Ditka?, Joe Schmidt?), unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic BRS-20 Tape 4 of ? (Box 46, Video 1063)
      - Dorset Cowboys Footage - Larry Elderidge, Five Minutes, unknown; Betacam SP 5 Minutes RT (Box 41, Video 887)
      - Chuck Scales Profile, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic Needs Case (Box 9, Video 143)
      - Chuck Scales Profile, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic BCA-30 (Box 21, Video 397)
      - Curtis martin Interview (And others) Tape 2, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute (Box 9, Video 274)
      - C Martin and others Tapei[sic] from BETV, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Needs Case (Box 9, Video 144)
      - Curtis Martin (WPXI), November 6, 1993; Betacam SP 20 Minute (Box 41, Video 874)
      - Hackett Recruiting #2, November 4, 1990; Betacam SP 20 Minute (Box 9, Video 279)
      - Hugh Green Interview, unknown; Betacam SP 20 Minute (Box 9, Video 290)
      - Hugh Green, unknown; Betacam SP 20 Minute (Box 41, Video 878)
      - Hugh Green Tribute (:24 Green Humored for H of F introduction / :59 Jersey Retired), unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute (Box 41, Video 896)
      - John Woodruff, unknown; VHS T-120 (Box 9, Video 150)
      - John Woodruff, unknown; Betacam SP 20 Minute (Box 41, Video 872)
      - John Woodruff - WPXI Raw Footage, unknown; VHS T-120 (Box 41, Video 876)
      - John Woodruff #1, unknown; Betacam SP 20 Minute (Box 41, Video 891)
      - John Woodruff #2, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute (Box 9, Video 177)
      - Pitt Prime Time, August 27, 1994; VHS T-60 (Box 9, Video 170)
      - University of Pittsburgh - Pitt Football 1995 2x :30, unknown; Betacam SP 2x :30 1. See for Yourself 2. Rest Easy (Box 9, Video 277)
      - Werner Brother PITT Football "Toughest" :30 TV, July 14, 1987; VHS :30 Needs Case (Box 9, Video 166)
      - Pittsburgh vs. Houston (1st Half), September 13, 1997; Betacam SP 90 Minute (Box 12, Video 192)
      - Pittsburgh vs. Houston (2nd Half), September 13, 1997; Betacam SP 90 Minute (Box 12, Video 193)
      - Pitt v. Miami, September 18, 1987; Betacam SP 90 Minute Tape 3 of ? (Box 12, Video 200)
      - Pittsburgh vs. VA Tech #1, November 22, 1997; Betacam SP 90 Minute Tape 1 of ? (Box 12, Video 197)
      - Pittsburgh vs. VA Tech #2, November 22, 1997; Betacam SP 90 Minute Tape 2 of ? (Box 12, Video 198)
      - Pittsburgh vs. VA Tech #3, November 22, 1997; Betacam SP 90 Minute Tape 3 of ? (Box 12, Video 195)
      - Pittsburgh vs. Penn State (2nd Half), September 6, 1997; Betacam SP 90 Minute Needs Case (Box 12, Video 194)
      - Pitt 8/30, August 20, 1997; Betacam SP 90 Minute Tape 1 of ? (Box 12, Video 199)
      - Pittsburgh vs. Syracuse #2, November 15, 1997; Betacam SP 90 Minute (Box 12, Video 202)
      - Pittsburgh vs. notre Dame Scoreboard Copy/Tape 1 of 3, October 11, 1997; Betacam SP 90 Minutes Opening Segment before Pitt vs. Notre Dame Game: Pitt vs. Miami on September 18, 1997 Needs Case (Box 12, Video 196)
      - Pittsburgh vs. notre Dame Scoreboard Copy/Tape 2 of 3, October 11, 1997; Betacam SP 90 Minute Tape 2 of 3 Needs Case (Box 12, Video 201)
      - Pittsburgh vs. notre Dame Scoreboard Copy/Tape 3 of 3, October 11, 1997; Betacam SP 90 Minute Tape 3 of 3 Needs Case (Box 12, Video 203)
      - Pitt vs. S. Miss., December 21, 1997; Betacam SP 90 Minute Needs Case (Box 12, Video 205)
      - Spring 1996 Pitt Offense Cut Ups G-Option 2 Minute Situation, unknown; VHS T-126E180 (Box 12, Video 206)
      - Pitt-WVU 1st Q, February 27, 1982?; 3/4 Inch U-matic Tape 1 of 4 (Box 13, Video 1982)
      - Pitt-WVU 2nd Q, February 27, 1982?; 3/4 Inch U-matic Tape 2 of 4 Needs Case (Box 13, Video 214)
      - Pitt-WVU 3rd Q, February 27, 1982?; 3/4 Inch U-matic Tape 3 of 4 Needs Case (Box 13, Video 213)
      - Pitt-WVU 4th Qt., February 27, 1982?; 3/4 Inch U-matic Tape 4 of 4 Needs Case (Box 13, Video 230)
      - Pitt - Penn St 83, 1983; 3/4 Inch U-matic Tape 1 of 4? Needs Case (Box 13, Video 207)
      - Pitt - Penn St 83, 1983; 3/4 Inch U-matic Tape 2 of 4? Needs Case (Box 13, Video 209)
      - Pitt - Penn St 83, 1983; 3/4 Inch U-matic Tape 4 of 4? Needs Case (Box 13, Video 212)
      - Pitt - Penn St 83, 1983; 3/4 Inch U-matic Needs Case (Box 13, Video 216)
      - Pitt vs. N.C. 1st Qtr., unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic Tape 1 of 4 Needs Case (Box 13, Video 229)
      - Pitt vs. N.C. 2nd Qtr., unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic Needs case (Box 13, Video 228)
      - Pitt vs. N.C. 3rd Qtr, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCA 60 Tape 3 of 4 Needs Case (Box 13, Video 215)
      - Pitt vs. N.C. 4th Qtr, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCA 60 Tape 4 of 4 Needs Case (Box 13, Video 217)
      - 1979 Pitt vs. Syracuse #1, 3/4 Inch U-matic Tape 1 of 4 Pittsburgh Penguins vs. Buffalo Sabres Hurley Interview Marino Interview Game Coverage (part 1) Needs Case (Box 13, Video 231)
      - 1979 Pitt vs. Syracuse #2, 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Tape 2 of 4 Needs Case (Box 13, Video 220)
      - 1979 Pitt vs. Syracuse #3, 3/4 Inch U-matic Tape 3 of 4 Needs Case (Box 13, Video 219)
      - 1979 Pitt vs. Syracuse #4, 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 30 Tape 4 of 4 Starts with 8:32 left in 4th quarter Needs case (Box 13, Video 224)
      - Hula Bowl 1983, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic Tape 2 of ? Needs Case (Box 13, Video 225)
      - Hula Bowl 1983, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic Tape 4 of ? (Box 13, Video 218)
      - Pitt - S. Carolina 1st Qtr., October 13, 1984; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Tape 1 of ? (Box 14, Video 1439)
      - Pitt - S. Carolina 2nd Qtr., October 13, 1984; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Tape 2 of ? (Box 14, Video 345)
      - Pitt - S. Carolina 3rd Qtr., October 13, 1984; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Tape 3 of ? (Box 14, Video 232)
      - Pitt - S. Carolina 4th Qtr., October 13, 1984; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Tape 4 of ? (Box 14, Video 233)
      - Pitt/Penn State Pre-game show 12:30 - 1:00, 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 30 (Box 14, Video 349)
      - Werner Brother, Inc. PITT Football "Toughest" :30 TV, July 14, 1987; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCA 10 (Box 14, Video 234)
      - It's a Winner (no update) 1978 Highlights Film, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 (Box 14, Video 307)
      - Pitt vs. WVU #1, September 26, 1987; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Tape 1 of ? (Box 14, Video 882)
      - Pitt vs. WVU #4, September 26, 1987; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Tape 4 of ? (Box 14, Video 235)
      - Pitt - Syracuse 3, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Tape 3 of ? Needs Case (Box 15, Video 255)
      - Pitt - Syracuse 4, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Tape 4 of ? Needs Case (Box 15, Video 250)
      - Football Season 1990, Betacam SP 5 Minute Needs Case (Box 15, Video 254)
      - Pitt Football, November 15, 1993; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCS 20 (Box 15, Video 256)
      - University of Pittsburgh Football, November 1, 1993; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 20 (Box 15, Video 257)
      - Pittsburgh vs. Houston - Hi-lights for the Big East, September 13, 1997; Betacam SP 30 Minute (Box 15, Video 240)
      - Pitt vs Rutgers Football at Pitt - Master Tape 2, October 13, 1990; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCA 60-XBR (Box 15, Video 239)
      - Pitt / Rutgers Highlights, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 20 (Box 15, Video 238)
      - Pitt Football Blood Drive, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCS 20 (Box 15, Video 302)
      - Pitt Football (Blood Drive), unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCS 20 (Box 15, Video 311)
      - "1991 Pitt Homecoming vs Syracuse", October 18, 1991; Betacam SP 30 Minute (Box 15, Video 249)
      - Pitt Camp #6 Wednesday AM, August 15, 1990; Betacam SP 20 Minute (Box 15, Video 243)
      - Pitt Camp #8 Wednesday PM, August 15, 1990; Betacam SP 20 Minute (Box 15, Video 253)
      - Football Recruiting Video 1988, unknown; VHS T-30 (Box 15, Video 251)
      - 1990 Football Season Tickets, unknown; VHS T-120 (Box 15, Video 248)
      - Pitt vs Syracuse Football #4, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-Matic KCS-20BRS Needs Case (Box 15, Video 247)
      - Pitt / Syracuse highlights Pitt / WVU highlights, unknown; VHS T-120 (Box 15, Video 245)
      - Music only (no video) For 1994 Football Highlight video, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Needs Case (Box 15, Video 246)
      - 1993 notre Dame Football Preview Video Tape, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute (Box 15, Video 269)
      - Football Head Shots 1993, Betacam SP (Box 15, Video 306)
      - Pitt - notre Dame 1st Half, unknown; Betacam SP Needs Case (Box 15, Video 242)
      - Pitt vs WVU Preview, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic MBR-20 Needs Case (Box 15, Video 241)
      - Pitt Aerials Football Stadium, unknown; Betacam SP 5 Minute (Box 15, Video 346)
      - Pitt vs Temple - Post-Game, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCS 20 (Box 15, Video 237)
      - Pitt / PSU Pregame, November 19, 1983; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 (Box 18, Video 315)
      - Pitt - N.D. 3, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic Tape 3 of 4 Needs Case (Box 18, Video 336)
      - Pitt vs. WVU, September 26, 1987; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Tape 2 of ? (Box 18, Video 319)
      - Pitt vs. WVU, September 26, 1987; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Tape 3 of ? (Box 18, Video 322)
      - Pitt - WVU - #1 ('83), 1983; 3/4 Inch U-matic Tape 1 of ? Needs Case (Box 42, Video 936)
      - Pitt - WVU #2 ('83), 1983; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Tape 2 of ? Needs Case (Box 42, Video 935)
      - Pitt - WVU ('83) 3, 1983; 3/4 Inch U-matic Tape 3 of ? (Box 42, Video 926)
      - Pitt - WVU '83 4, 1983; 3/4 Inch U-matic Tape 4 of 4 Needs Case (Box 18, Video 334)
      - Great American Independent Football '89, October 7, 1989; 3/4 Inch U-matic Pitt vs. Temple Tape 1 of 4 (Box 18, Video 316)
      - Only the Beginning, March 4, 1986; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 30 1974 Pitt Highlights (Box 18, Video 317)
      - Fiesta Bowl II - Pitt vs. Arizona OR Panther Pride and W "Pitt vs. Cincinnati 9/19/81", [DVD Available], December 25, 1979 OR September 19, 1981; 3/4 Inch U-matic XL (Box 18, Video 318)
      - 1979 Fiesta Bowl Part III - Pitt vs. Arizona, December 25, 1979; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 (Box 34, Video 690)
      - "Pitt Football: A Tradition" (1984 Pitt Highlights Show), unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 30 (Box 18, Video 320)
      - Pitt Football: A Tradition, August 23, 1985; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 (Box 18, Video 321)
      - University of Pittsburgh vs. University of Texas, September 3, 1994; Betacam SP 60 Minute 12:00-1:00 Tape 1 of 4 (Box 18, Video 324)
      - University of Pittsburgh vs. University of Texas, September 3, 1994; Betacam SP 60 Minute 1:00-2:00 Tape 2 of 4 (Box 18, Video 323)
      - University of Pittsburgh vs. University of Texas, September 3, 1994; Betacam SP 60 Minute 3:00-4:00 Tape 4 of 4 (Box 18, Video 325)
      - 82 Pitt - Penn St 1, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic 35 Millimeter Tape Tape 1 of 4 Needs Case (Box 34, Video 693)
      - 82 Pitt Penn St 2, 1982; 3/4 Inch U-matic Tape 2 of 4 Needs Case (Box 18, Video 331)
      - 82 Pitt Penn St 3, 1982; 3/4 Inch U-matic Tape 3 of 4 Needs Case (Box 18, Video 328)
      - 82 Pitt Penn St 4, 1982; 3/4 Inch U-matic Tape 4 of 4 Needs Case (Box 18, Video 333)
      - Pitt - Tenn 1, September 3, 1983; 3/4 Inch U-matic Tape 1 of 4 Needs Case (Box 18, Video 329)
      - Pitt - Tenn 2, September 3, 1983; 3/4 Inch U-matic Tape 2 of 4 Needs Case (Box 18, Video 330)
      - Pitt - Tenn 3, September 3, 1983; 3/4 Inch U-matic Tape 3 of 4 Needs Case (Box 18, Video 327)
      - Pitt Tenn 4, September 3, 1983; 3/4 Inch U-matic 60 Minute Tape 4 of 4 Needs Case (Box 18, Video 332)
      - Texas vs Pittsburgh - 1994 End Zone, VHS ST120 (Box 20, Video 355)
      - Texas vs Pittsburgh - 1994 Wide Sideline, VHS ST-120 (Box 20, Video 359)
      - Pittsburgh Kick / Texas Kick, September 16, 1995; Betacam SP 30 Minute IC Needs Case (Box 20, Video 363)
      - Penn State PAT / Field Goal Block - 1996, VHS ST-126 (Box 20, Video 356)
      - Spring 1996 Pitt Offense Cut Ups - Shortyardage G-Trap/G-Option, unknown; VHS ST-120 (Box 20, Video 357)
      - Pitt Football 2X:30 - 1. See for Yourself / 2. Rest Easy, unknown; VHS T-10 (Box 20, Video 358)
      - 1994 Pitt Offense vs. Boston College, September 24, 1994; Betacam SP 30 Minute Intercut Tape 1 of 2 Needs Case (Box 20, Video 366)
      - 1994 Pitt Offense vs. Boston College, September 24, 1994; Betacam SP 30 Minute Intercut Tape 2 of 2 Needs Case (Box 20, Video 367)
      - 1994 Pitt Offense vs. Louisville, October 1, 1994; Betacam SP 30 Minute Intercut Tape 1 of 2 Needs Case (Box 20, Video 364)
      - 1994 Pitt Offense vs. Louisville, October 1, 1994; Betacam SP 30 Minute Intercut Tape 2 of 2 Needs Case (Box 20, Video 365)
      - 1994 Pitt Offense vs. Ohio, September 10, 1994; Betacam SP 30 Minute Intercut Tape 1 of 2 Needs Case (Box 20, Video 368)
      - 1994 Pitt Offense vs. Rutgers, November 19, 1994; Betacam SP 30 Minute IC Needs Case (Box 20, Video 361)
      - 1994 Pitt Offense vs. Rutgers, November 19, 1994; Betacam SP 30 Minute Intercut Tape 2 of 2 Needs Case (Box 20, Video 360)
      - 1994 Pitt Offense vs. Syracuse, October 8, 1994; Betacam SP 30 Minute Intercut Needs Case (Box 20, Video 369)
      - Pittsburgh Offense 2N H / Rutgers Defense, October 28, 1995; Betacam SP 30 Minute IC Needs Case (Box 20, Video 362)
      - 1995 Season Swing Route Tracking, unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Needs Case (Box 20, Video 373)
      - 1992 Football Halftime Feature - Paul Hackett "Hackett's Top 40", October 31, 1992; Betacam SP PB 5 (Box 21, Video 370)
      - Pitt - Syracuse 1 (Tape 1, Defensive Coordinator), unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Tape 1 of 2 Needs Case (Box 21, Video 374)
      - Pitt - Syracuse 2 (Tape 2, Defensive Coordinator), unknown; Betacam SP 30 Minute Tape 2 of 2 Needs Case (Box 21, Video 375)
      - Pittsburgh Football Halftimes - 1991 - 1. Jim Royal / 2. Paul Hackett, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 20s (Box 21, Video 377)
      - "Pitt vs Temple" (November 10, 1990) (Tape #2), Betacam SP 90 Minute (Box 21, Video 380)
      - Pitt vs. WVU #1, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic MBR 20s Needs Case (Box 21, Video 382)
      - Pitt vs WVU #2, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 (Box 21, Video 379)
      - Mark Spindler - University of Pittsburgh Defensive Tackle Video Footage, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic BCS 20 (Box 21, Video 381)
      - Tony Woods Interview, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic Needs Case (Box 21, Video 388)
      - Pitts vs Louisville Quarter #1, October 1, 1994; 3/4 Inch U-Matic KCA 60 Tape 1 of 4 (Box 15, Video 236)
      - Pitt vs. Louisville - Quarter #2, October 1, 1994; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCA 60 Tape 2 of 4 (Box 21, Video 394)
      - Pitt vs. Louisville - Quarter #3, October 1, 1994; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCA 60 Tape 3 of 4 (Box 21, Video 396)
      - Pitt vs. Louisville - Quarter #4, October 1, 1994; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCA 60 Tape 4 of 4 (Box 21, Video 395)
      - Pitt - Syracuse Ground Level Hilites (1989), 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA-20s (Box 21, Video 399)
      - Pitt Football Highlights, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic (Box 21, Video 400)
      - Big East News Feed Pitt Football, November 7, 1994; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCS 20 Master (Box 22, Video 404)
      - Pitt Football Big East Feed, September 26, 1994; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCS 20 Master (Box 22, Video 405)
      - Big East News Feed, October 10, 1994; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCS 20 (Box 22, Video 406)
      - Pitt vs. Notre Dame / Kent State / Rutgers, unknown; Betacam SP 20 Minute (Box 22, Video 402)
      - Pitt / Penn St. Pre-Game Show "Battle for the Eastern Front", unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Needs Case (Box 23, Video 416)
      - How Sweet It Is - 1981-1982 (Sugar Bowl Pre-game Show), unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 30 (Box 22, Video 403)
      - "Pitt vs Oklahoma" (Tape #1), September 15, 1990; Betacam SP 90 Minute Tape 1 of ? (Box 23, Video 417)
      - Gator Bowl, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 30 Tape 1 of ? (Box 23, Video 418)
      - "Gator Bowl" 1980, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic 30 Minute Tape 2 of ? (Box 23, Video 428)
      - 1980 Gator Bowl #1, 3/4 Inch U-matic 60 Minute Tape 1 of ? (Box 24, Video 468)
      - Pitt Highlights #1 - Pitt / BYU 1984, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 20 (Box 23, Video 491)
      - Pitt - Syracuse 1st Quarter, November 3, 1984; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 (Box 23, Video 419)
      - Pitt - Syracuse 4th Quarter, November 3, 1984; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 (Box 23, Video 420)
      - "John Hancock Bowl" (Tape #1), December 30, 1989; 3/4 Inch U-matic KCA-60BRS Tape 1 of ? (Box 23, Video 471)
      - Pitt - Miami 1st Quarter, October 20, 1984; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 (Box 23, Video 421)
      - "Pitt vs Boston College" (Tape #1), September 8, 1990; Betacam SP 60 Minute Tape 1 of 3 (Box 23, Video 426)
      - "Pitt vs Boston College" (Tape #2), September 8, 1990; Betacam SP 90 Minute Tape 2 of 3 (Box 23, Video 427)
      - Pitt / Florida State - Reel #2, September 18, 1982; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Tape 2 of ? (Box 23, Video 501)
      - Pittsburgh - WV, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Tape 3 of 4 (Box 23, Video 470)
      - Fiesta Bowl Part II, December 13, 1979; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Tape 2 of ? (Box 23, Video 422)
      - PITT vs Penn State, November 28, 1980; 3/4 Inch U-matic 60 Minute Tape 2 of 4 (Box 24, Video 433)
      - Sugar Bowl (Pitt vs. GA), January 1, 1977; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Tape 1 of 4 (Box 24, Video 473)
      - Sugar Bowl (Pitt vs. GA), January 1, 1977; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Tape 3 of 4 (Box 24, Video 449)
      - Goldberg, VHS 120SHG (Box 24, Video 459)
      - Year of the Panther (1976 Highlights, Pitt Football J. Mayors[sic]), December 15, 1976 AND December 27, 1976; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 (Box 24, Video 461)
      - 33 Annual[sic] Gator Bowl 1977, [DVD Available], December 30, 1977; Betacam SP 30 Minute (Box 25, Video 493)
      - 1977 Gator Bowl - Pitt / Clemson - 3 of 4, December 30, 1977; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Tape 3 of 4 (Box 25, Video 481)
      - 1977 Gator Bowl - Pitt / Clemson 1 of 4, December 30, 1977; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Tape 1 of 4 Needs Case (Box 25, Video 474)
      - 1977 Gator Bowl - Pitt / Clemson - 2 of 4, December 30, 1977; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Tape 2 of 4 (Box 25, Video 483)
      - 1977 Gator Bowl - Pitt vs Clemson, December 30, 1977; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Tape 4 of 4 (Box 24, Video 464)
      - Gator Bowl Part 4 - Pitt vs. Clemson, December 30, 1978; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 Tape 4 of ? (Box 25, Video 487)
      - Pitt Football 1978, unknown; Betacam SP 20 Minute (Box 25, Video 477)
      - Pitt vs Florida State 1978, Betacam SP 30 Minute (Box 25, Video 479)
      - Pitt Films - Notre Dame / Pitt 1944, Indiana / Pitt 1945, unknown; 3/4 Inch U-matic UCA 60 (Box 25, Video 484)
      - Anthony Dorsett, D. Jells, Jay Jones - ICYA Indoor Meet of Syracuse (Carrier Dome) - 1995, Betacam SP 30 Minute (Box 26, Video 498)
      - Pitt vs. West Virginia, September 30, 1989; VHS T-120 31-31 (Box 26, Video 531)
      - Pitt vs. Southern Mississippi - Johnny Majors First Game, unknown; VHS T-120 (Box 26, Video 527)
      - Pitt / Miami #1, September 18, 1997; Betacam SP 90 Minute Tape 1 of ? (Box 26, Video 514)